<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_PARTNER_MARRIAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
	    Hey Lilaya, does the concept of marriage exist here in dominion?
         Lilaya's cheecks turn a tinge red, what? yes of cource PC name. couples get married all the time
         Oh good, I wasn't sure if it was a thing
            INNOCENT/SHY considering... you gesture your hand to refer to everything, the culture here
            ELSE        considering how everyone seems to be fucking someone new everyday
    </p>
	<p>
        mmm, sure there is a lot of... causal romance going on in our world, but like I said before, there are plently of couples who decide to dedicate themselves for life.
		 Well, some couples are more open to fooling about, and some are more excusionary, notwithstanding the occasional arccane storm. That's just a part of life, 
        but I'm sure we still have some things in commom, like proposing, taking your betrhothed to a church or someplace similar, exchanging your vows, and then going off to a honeymoon
        you nod in the affermitive
	</p>
	<p>
        So uh, how come you ask PC?
        I like my partner NPC a lot, and i stiil plan on ggoing home, its just that they mean a lot to me and i want to show them that our bond means something
        oh PC, congradulations, lilaya says hugging you
	</p>
	<p>
		so how do you get married here? any thing special rules or traditions that i should know about?
        oh certainly, considering you don't have lilin, i imagine this is different to how it was back on your home world, but marriages usually happen in a day
        noting the puzzled look on your face, she continues, uh well, tradition states tht you're meant to surprise your betrothed. this comes from an ancient incident where a lilin was swept of her feet and married that day"
					+ "forbidden lilin marriage, she was swept away one day and married that afternoon, so the ceremony is the same (having to surprise the bride)"
        though you can't just marry anyone, worker protection laws mean you cant marry your own or someone else's slaves. And although you are meant to swwep them of their feet, you can't force them to marry you; no means no.
	</p>
	<p>
        So who do i plan the wedding through?
        well we do have dedicated wedding vendors and specailists, hmm, i just can't think of any off the top of of my headd though
	</p>
	<p>
        coming to the rescure of her master, Rose speaks up. mistress, I do know of a particularly good wedding vendor
		Dream Lover, at the shopping mall is both quality and reasonable prices"
		rose, how do you know this?, lilaya asks blushing, and suddenly finding her tail interesting to play with
		one of my siblings used it, do you remember my sister lily? Though she did warn me that although the owner goes above and beyond in quality, they're a bit... temperamental;
    </p>
	<p>
        well PC, looks like you know where to go now. If you need anymore help, feel free to talk to me at any time
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unlike the rest of the buildings in the Arcade, the one in front of you has no real storefront to speak of, and the only indication of it being a shop at all is the rather plain-looking sign above the entrance bearing the name 'Dream Lover'. It's not like the place is in a state of decay, so you can't say that it's the worst looking shop you've ever seen, although it would definitely be in the running for the blandest.
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking a closer inspection of the property, you can't find any information that reveals the shop's working hours, or even what sort of goods are stocked here. Despite all of this, there's also no indication that the store is closed, so you could try taking a look inside if you wanted to.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR_CLOSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Intrigued by the thought of what this store might offer, you walk up to the entrance and give the door knob a tentative twist; to your dismay, you discover that the store is [style.colourBad(closed)], leaving you with no other option but to step back and consider returning at a later time.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had enough of this store for now, you turn to look at Ashley, wondering if you should wave them goodbye.
		 You doubt you'll get any response, but, considering that you're the only two people here, it seems a little impolite not to say anything, so you call out,
		 [pc.speech(I'll be leaving now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Ashley doesn't look at you, but you hear them mutter,
		 [Ashley.speech(Feel free to come back any time.)]
		 It's a passionless plea, more like a social obligation than anything else, but at least they said something back.
	</p>
	<p>
		With a sigh of relief, you finally leave the building and the rude owner within it.
		 As you step outside, you reflect on the fact that this is the only store of its kind in the Arcade, and even if you never get a lover, you could perhaps find a use for the sex toys...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
</dialogue>
