<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLUBBER_START_DATING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		hey npc, i know we've only known each other for a short while, but I really enjoy spending time with you.
		 You're really hot, handsome, kind, and you know how to show a [pc.guy] a good time.
		 I guess what I'm trying to say is that I really like you, will you be my boyfriend?
	</p>
    <p>
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN npc's hands shoot up to her face as it goes bright red, [npc.speech(O-Oh, oh my, [pc.name], I a um!)] Giving npc a disarming smile, she lowers her hand behind her back [npc.speech(Hi! H-How are you doing? I came here with a friend, but they left me standing alone again...)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN Although npc is usally pretty confident, your confession has got him blushing like a schoolboy, [npc.speech([pc.Name]! Hi again! How are you doing?!)]
			#ELSE npc isn't the most confident of people, but you confession has turned him red as a post box, [npc.speech(Oh, [pc.name]! I can't belive it, yes!)] they say, throwing their arms around you
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
    <p>
        [npc.speech(So um... What should me do now?)] npc says, blushing and twidling his fingers. You could spend the rest of the night here at the club, or go back home with your new boyfriend.
    </p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLUBBER_DOM_START_DATING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		hey npc, i know we've only known each other for a short while, but I really enjoy spending time with you.
		 You're really hot, handsome, kind, and you know how to show a [pc.guy] a good time.
		 This is hard for even me to say, but I really like you, will you be my boyfriend?
	</p>
    <p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN A large smile breaks out on npc's face, [npc.speech(wow, [pc.name], I'm at a loss for words, that was really touching. you're cute, adorable and smart and I would be honoured to be your boyfriend.)] [npc.Name] takes hold of your hands and leans in and kisses you. You start kissing him back as you embrace each other under the clubs strobing lights. Breaking off the kiss, Npc speaks, [npc.speech(It's getting a bit too crowded in here for my liking, how about we go back to my place and... unwind.)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Well damn, [pc.babe(npc)], after that, how could I say no. Yeah, I'll be your [npc.man])] npc says, before leaning in and kissing you. [npc.His] tongue abruptly surges forward, and you're suddenly making out with your new boyfriend. Breaking off to let you breathe, [npc.speech(now how could I leave such a cute boy/girl like you here, how 'bout we find go back to mine and I can show you how a real [npc.man] treats [npc.his]#IF(pc.isFeminine()!=npc.isFeminine()) [pc.woman].#ELSE [pc.girlfriend].#ENDIF)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Aw gosh, [pc.name], that was really touching. I would love to be your boyfriend.)] npc says before placing his hands on your hips and pulling you in for a kiss. You start kissing him back as you embrace each other under the clubs strobing lights. Breaking off the kiss, Npc speaks huskily, [npc.speech(Hey, how about we head on over to my place and I can <i>really</i> show you how much I love you)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
    <p>
        Npc obviously has some thoughts on what do do for the rest of the night. you could either go with [npc.his] flow, or speak up now and decide what to do for the rest of the night with your new boyfirend.
    </p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
